virtualpiano.net 2017-12-10

# Privacy and Information | Virtual Piano

**Virtual Piano (or its holding company Crystal Magic Studio Ltd)** may collect personal information from you through this website. For example, if you register with us in order to receive news and announcements, your information will be stored either manually or electronically. 

Virtual Piano also uses cookies to personalise content, features and experiences. Where applicable, the website uses a cookie control system allowing the user on their first visit to allow or disallow the use of cookies. This complies with legislation requirements for websites to obtain explicit consent from users before leaving behind or reading files such as cookies on a user’s computer/device.

Any personal information you give to us through the applications on this site will always be processed in accordance with the UK Data Protection Act 1998. We will only use the personal information you provide to deliver the services you have requested, or for our lawful, disclosed purposes. We will not make your personal details available outside our organisation without your consent, unless obliged to by law.

This website will automatically track certain information about you in the course of you using this website, such as your IP address and browser identification. This information is used only for preventing malicious attacks, for system administration and for providing statistics to evaluate use of this site.

Cookies are small files saved to the user’s computer’s hard drive that track, save and store information about the user’s interactions and usage of the website. This allows the website, through its server to provide the users with a tailored experience within this website. Users are advised that if they wish to deny the use and saving of cookies from this website, they should take necessary steps within their web browsers security settings to block all cookies from this website and its external serving vendors. The tracking software used is provided by Google Analytics which uses cookies to track visitor usage. The software will save a cookie to your computer’s hard drive in order to track and monitor your engagement and usage of the website, but will not store, save or collect personal information. Other cookies may be stored to your computer’s hard drive by external vendors when this website uses referral programs, sponsored links or adverts. Such cookies are used for conversion and referral tracking and typically expire after 30 days, though some may take longer. No personal information is stored, saved or collected.

If you would like to delete the cookies this website has stored on your computer, you can simply do so by clicking **_[Delete Cookies]()_** (You will not see an acknowledgement of deletion). If you continue to use the website, we’ll assume you’re happy with the cookies that we set.

* * *

Also see:
